so what are these benchmarks they're
programs an input data that users or
companies have agreed upon will be used
for performance measurements so pretty
much either a consortium of companies
meets and decides that these are the
programs and input data that we will use
for performance measurements or a group
of people who is concerned about some
performance issue will design programs
and data and allow others to measure
performance on that type of a problem
using those programs and input data
usually we don't have just one benchmark
program we have a benchmark suite it
consists of multiple programs along with
their input data each of these programs
is usually chosen to be representative
of some type of applications so for
example we will not have ten different
compression programs in a benchmark we
will usually have one or two because we
think that those one or two are probably
accurately representing the behavior of
the other compression programs that we
didn't put in the benchmark suite